Collis Potter Huntington Papers
Collis Potter Huntington Papers
- Correspondence
  - July 15-31 1869, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Aug 1869, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Sep 1869 (Box 3)
  - Oct 1869 (Box 3)
  - Nov 1869, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Dec 1869, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Jan 2-31 1870, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Feb 1870, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Mar 1870, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Apr 1870, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - May 1870, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - June 1870, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - July 1870, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Aug 1-15, 17-31 1870, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Sep 1-28 1870 (Box 5)
  - Oct 1870, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Nov 1870, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Dec 1-30 1870, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Jan 1871, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Feb 1871, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Mar 1-30 1871, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Apr 1871, 5 folders (Box 6)
  - May 1871, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - June 1871, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - July 1871, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Aug 1871, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Sep 1871, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Oct 1-21, 23-31 1871, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Nov 1871, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Dec 1-30 1871, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Jan 1872, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Feb 1872, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Mar 1872, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Apr 1872, 5 folders (Box 9)
  - May 1872, 5 folders (Box 9)
  - June 1-8, 10-29 1872, 5 folders (Box 9)
  - July 1872, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Aug 1-17, 19-31 1872, 5 folders (Box 10)
  - Sep 1872, 5 folders (Box 10)
  - Oct 1872, 5 folders (Box 10)
  - Nov 1872, 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Dec 1872, 5 folders (Box 11)
  - Jan 1873, 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Feb 1873, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Mar 1873, 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Apr 1873, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - May 1873, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - June 1873, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - July 1873, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Aug 1-30 1873, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Sep 1873, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Oct 1873, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Nov 1873, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Dec 1873, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Jan 1874, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Feb 1874, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Mar 1874, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Apr 1874, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - May 1874, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - June 1874, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - July 1874, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Aug 1874, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Sep 1874, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Oct 1874, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Nov 1874, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Dec 1874, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Jan 1875, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Feb 1-27 1875, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Mar 1875, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Apr 1875, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - May 1875, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - June 1-8, 11-31 1875, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - July 1875, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Aug 1875, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Sep 1875, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Oct 1-30 1875, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Nov 1875, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Dec 1875, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Jan 1876, 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Feb 1876, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Mar 1876, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Apr 1876, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - May 1876, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - June 1876, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - July 1876, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Aug 1-17 1876, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Aug 18-31 1876, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Sep 1876, 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Oct 1876, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Nov 1876, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Dec 1876, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Jan 1877, 5 folders (Box 21)
  - Feb 1877, 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Mar 1877, 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Apr 1877, 4 folders (Box 21)
  - May 1877, 5 folders (Box 22)
  - June 1877, 4 folders (Box 22)
  - July 1877, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Aug 1877, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Sep 1877, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Oct 1877, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Nov 1877, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Dec 1877, 4 folders (Box 24)
  - Jan 1878, 7 folders (Box 24)
  - Feb 1878, 4 folders (Box 24)
  - Mar 1878, 5 folders (Box 25)
  - Apr 1878, 5 folders (Box 25)
  - May 1878, 5 folders (Box 25)
  - June 1878, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - July 1-30 1878, 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Aug 1878, 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Sep 1878, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Oct 1878, 5 folders (Box 27)
  - Nov 1878, 6 folders (Box 27)
  - Dec 1878, 7 folders (Box 28)
  - Jan 1879, 8 folders (Box 28)
  - Feb 1879, 6 folders (Box 29)
  - Mar 1879, 6 folders (Box 29)
  - Apr 1-5, 7-30 1879, 5 folders (Box 30)
  - May 1879, 4 folders (Box 30)
  - June 1879, 5 folders (Box 30)
  - July 1879, 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Aug 1879, 3 folders (Box 31)
  - Sep 1879, 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Oct 1879, 4 folders (Box 32)
  - Nov 1879, 5 folders (Box 32)
  - Dec 1879, 6 folders (Box 33)
  - Jan 1880, 7 folders (Box 33)
  - Feb 1880, 6 folders (Box 34)
  - Mar 1880, 6 folders (Box 34)
  - Apr 1880, 7 folders (Box 35)
  - May 1880, 8 folders (Box 35)
  - June 1880, 7 folders (Box 36)
  - July 1880, 6 folders (Box 36)
  - Aug 1880, 4 folders (Box 37)
  - Sep 1880, 5 folders (Box 37)
  - Oct 1880, 6 folders (Box 38)
  - Nov 1880, 8 folders (Box 38)
  - Dec 1880, 8 folders (Box 39)
  - Jan 1-15 1881, 5 folders (Box 39)
  - Jan 16-31 1881, 5 folders (Box 40)
  - Feb 1881, 9 folders (Box 40)
  - Mar 1881, 6 folders (Box 41)
  - Apr 1881, 10 folders (Box 42)
  - May 1881, 9 folders (Box 43)
  - June 1881, 11 folders (Box 44)
  - July 1881, 9 folders (Box 45)
  - Aug 1-15 1881, 4 folders (Box 45)
  - Aug 16-31 1881, 4 folders (Box 46)
  - Sep 1881, 13 folders (Box 46)
  - Oct 1881, 10 folders (Box 47)
  - Nov 1881, 8 folders (Box 48)
  - Dec 1881, 10 folders (Box 49)
  - Jan 1882, 10 folders (Box 50)
  - Feb 1882, 8 folders (Box 51)
  - Mar 1882, 7 folders (Box 51)
  - Apr 1882, 9 folders (Box 52)
  - May 1-14 1882, 4 folders (Box 52)
  - May 15-31 1882, 5 folders (Box 53)
  - June 1-14 1882, 5 folders (Box 53)
  - June 15-30 1882, 5 folders (Box 54)
  - July 1882, 8 folders (Box 54)
  - Aug 1882, 5 folders (Box 55)
  - Sep 1882, 7 folders (Box 55)
  - Oct 1882, 10 folders (Box 56)
  - Nov 1882, 8 folders (Box 57)
  - Dec 1882, 8 folders (Box 58)
  - Jan 1883, 8 folders (Box 59)
  - Feb 1883, 8 folders (Box 60)
  - Mar 1-15 1883, 5 folders (Box 60)
  - Mar 16-31 1883, 5 folders (Box 61)
  - Apr 1883, 8 folders (Box 61)
  - May 1883, 9 folders (Box 62)
  - June 1883, 7 folders (Box 63)
  - July 1883, 11 folders (Box 64)
  - Aug 1883, 10 folders (Box 65)
  - Sep 1883, 6 folders (Box 66)
  - Oct 1883, 7 folders (Box 66)
  - Nov 1883, 7 folders (Box 67)
  - Dec 1883, 11 folders (Box 68)
  - Jan 1884, 10 folders (Box 69)
  - Feb 1884, 13 folders (Box 70)
  - Mar 1884, 8 folders (Box 71)
  - Apr 1884, 12 folders (Box 72)
  - May 1884, 12 folders (Box 73)
  - June 1884, 10 folders (Box 74)
  - July 1884, 12 folders (Box 75)
  - Aug 1-30 1884, 12 folders (Box 76)
  - Sep 1884, 11 folders (Box 77)
  - Oct 1-15 1884, 4 folders (Box 77)
  - Oct 16-31 1884, 4 folders (Box 78)
  - Nov 1884, 7 folders (Box 78)
  - Dec 1884, 9 folders (Box 79)
  - Jan 1885, 13 folders (Box 80)
  - Feb 1885, 12 folders (Box 81)
  - Mar 1885, 13 folders (Box 82)
  - Apr 1885, 8 folders (Box 83)
  - May 1-30 1885, 8 folders (Box 83)
  - June 1885, 7 folders (Box 84)
  - July 1885, 8 folders (Box 84)
  - Aug 1885, 8 folders (Box 85)
  - Sep 1885, 6 folders (Box 85)
  - Oct 1885, 6 folders (Box 86)
  - Nov 1885, 8 folders (Box 86)
  - Dec 1885, 11 folders (Box 87)
  - Jan 1886, 8 folders (Box 88)
  - Feb 1886, 7 folders (Box 89)
  - Mar 1886, 6 folders (Box 89)
  - Apr 1886, 7 folders (Box 90)
  - May 1886, 6 folders (Box 90)
  - June 1886, 7 folders (Box 91)
  - July 1886, 8 folders (Box 91)
  - Aug 1886, 6 folders (Box 92)
  - Sep 1886, 7 folders (Box 93)
  - Oct 1886, 4 folders (Box 93)
  - Nov 1886, 6 folders (Box 94)
  - Dec 1886, 8 folders (Box 94)
  - Jan 1887, 10 folders (Box 95)
  - Feb 1887, 8 folders (Box 96)
  - Mar 1887, 8 folders (Box 97)
  - Apr 1887, 4 folders (Box 98)
  - May 1887, 6 folders (Box 98)
  - June 1887, 5 folders (Box 99)
  - July 1887, 5 folders (Box 99)
  - Aug 1887, 5 folders (Box 100)
  - Sep 1887, 3 folders (Box 100)
  - Oct 1887, 4 folders (Box 100)
  - Nov 1887, 4 folders (Box 101)
  - Dec 1887, 4 folders (Box 101)
  - Jan 1888, 5 folders (Box 102)
  - Feb 1888, 5 folders (Box 102)
  - Mar 1888, 5 folders (Box 102)
  - Apr 1888, 4 folders (Box 103)
  - May 1888, 3 folders (Box 103)
  - June 1-22, 25-30 1888, 3 folders (Box 103)
  - July 1888, 3 folders (Box 104)
  - Aug 1888, 4 folders (Box 104)
  - Sep 1-29 1888, 3 folders (Box 104)
  - Oct 1888, 3 folders (Box 105)
  - Nov 1888, 2 folders (Box 105)
  - Dec 1888, 3 folders (Box 105)
  - Jan 1889, 5 folders (Box 105)
  - Feb 1889, 3 folders (Box 106)
  - Mar 1889, 3 folders (Box 106)
  - Apr 1889, 3 folders (Box 106)
  - May 1889, 3 folders (Box 107)
  - June 1889, 2 folders (Box 107)
  - July 1889, 4 folders (Box 107)
  - Aug 1889, 2 folders (Box 107)
  - Sep 1889 (Box 108)
  - Oct 1-29 1889 (Box 108)
  - Nov 1-29 1889 (Box 108)
  - Dec 1-16, 18-31 1889, 2 folders (Box 108)
  - Jan 1890, 2 folders (Box 108)
  - Feb 1890 (Box 108)
  - Mar 1890 (Box 108)
  - Apr 1890, 2 folders (Box 108)
  - May 1890, 3 folders (Box 109)
  - June 1890, 4 folders (Box 109)
  - July 1890, 3 folders (Box 109)
  - Aug 1890, 3 folders (Box 110)
  - Sep 1890, 2 folders (Box 110)
  - Oct 1890, 3 folders (Box 110)
  - Nov 1890, 3 folders (Box 110)
  - Dec 1890, 3 folders (Box 111)
  - Jan 1891, 6 folders (Box 111)
  - Feb 1891, 3 folders (Box 112)
  - Mar 1891, 4 folders (Box 112)
  - Apr 1891, 4 folders (Box 112)
  - May 1891, 4 folders (Box 113)
  - June 1891, 3 folders (Box 113)
  - July 1891, 5 folders (Box 113)
  - Aug 1891, 3 folders (Box 114)
  - Sep 1891, 3 folders (Box 114)
  - Oct 1891, 3 folders (Box 114)
  - Nov 1891, 3 folders (Box 115)
  - Dec 1891, 4 folders (Box 115)
  - Jan 1892, 4 folders (Box 115)
  - Feb 1-20, 22-29 1892, 4 folders (Box 116)
  - Mar 1892, 4 folders (Box 116)
  - Apr 1892, 4 folders (Box 116)
  - May 1892, 4 folders (Box 117)
  - June 1892, 4 folders (Box 117)
  - July 1892, 4 folders (Box 117)
  - Aug 1892, 4 folders (Box 118)
  - Sep 1892, 5 folders (Box 118)
  - Oct 1892, 6 folders (Box 118)
  - Nov 1892, 2 folders (Box 119)
  - Dec 1892, 3 folders (Box 119)
  - Jan 1893, 3 folders (Box 119)
  - Feb 1893, 4 folders (Box 120)
  - Mar 1893, 5 folders (Box 120)
  - Apr 1893, 4 folders (Box 120)
  - May 1893, 4 folders (Box 121)
  - June 1893, 4 folders (Box 121)
  - July 1893, 5 folders (Box 121)
  - Aug 1893, 2 folders (Box 122)
  - Sep 1893, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Oct 1893, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Nov 1893, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Dec 1893, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Jan 1894, 4 folders (Box 123)
  - Feb 1894, 3 folders (Box 123)
  - Mar 1894, 4 folders (Box 123)
  - Apr 1894, 5 folders (Box 124)
  - May 1894, 3 folders (Box 124)
  - June 1894 (Box 124)
  - July 1894 (Box 125)
  - Aug 1894 (Box 125)
  - Sep 1894 (Box 125)
  - Oct 1894 (Box 125)
  - Nov 1894 (Box 125)
  - Dec 1894 (Box 125)
  - Jan 1895 (Box 125)
  - Feb 1895, 3 folders (Box 125)
  - Mar 1895, 4 folders (Box 125)
  - Apr 1-26 1895, 2 folders (Box 126)
  - May 1895 (Box 126)
  - June 1895 (Box 126)
  - July 1-30 1895 (Box 126)
  - Sep 1895 (Box 126)
  - Oct 1895 (Box 126)
  - Nov 1895 (Box 126)
  - Dec 1895 (Box 126)
  - Jan 1896, 2 folders (Box 126)
  - Feb 1896 (Box 126)
  - Mar 1896 (Box 127)
  - Apr 1896, 3 folders (Box 127)
  - May 1896, 2 folders (Box 127)
  - June 1896 (Box 127)
  - July 1896 (Box 127)
  - Aug 1896 (Box 127)
  - Sep 1896 (Box 127)
  - Oct 1-30 1896 (Box 127)
  - Nov 1896 (Box 127)
  - Dec 1896 (Box 127)
  - Jan 1897 (Box 127)
  - Feb 1897 (Box 128)
  - Mar 1897 (Box 128)
  - Apr 1897 (Box 128)
  - May 1897 (Box 128)
  - June 1897 (Box 128)
  - July 1897 (Box 128)
  - Aug 1897 (Box 128)
  - Sep 1897 (Box 128)
  - Oct 1897 (Box 128)
  - Nov 1897 (Box 128)
  - Dec 1897 (Box 128)
  - Jan 1898 (Box 128)
  - Feb 1898 (Box 128)
  - Mar 1898 (Box 128)
  - Apr 1898 (Box 128)
  - May 1898 (Box 128)
  - June 1-29 1898 (Box 128)
  - July 3-30 1898 (Box 129)
  - Aug 3-30 1898 (Box 129)
  - Sep 1-28 1898 (Box 129)
  - Oct 3-31 1898 (Box 129)
  - Nov 1898 (Box 129)
  - Dec 1898 (Box 129)
  - Jan 1899 (Box 129)
  - Feb 1899 (Box 129)
  - Mar 1899 (Box 129)
  - Apr 1-29 1899, 2 folders (Box 129)
  - May 1-30 1899 (Box 129)
  - June 1-28 1899 (Box 130)
  - July 5-29 1899 (Box 130)
  - Aug 1899 (Box 130)
  - Sep 6-29 1899 (Box 130)
  - Oct 1-30 1899 (Box 130)
  - Nov 1-29 1899 (Box 130)
  - Dec 5-29 1899 (Box 130)
  - Jan 3-31 1900 (Box 130)
  - Feb 1-27 1900 (Box 130)
  - Mar 2-31 1900, 2 folders (Box 130)
  - Apr 2-30 1900, 2 folders (Box 130)
  - May 1900 (Box 131)
  - June 1900 (Box 131)
  - July 1900 (Box 131)
  - Aug 1900, 2 folders (Box 131)
  - Sep 1900 (Box 131)
  - Oct 1900 (Box 131)
  - Nov 1900 (Box 131)
  - Dec 1900 (Box 131)
  - Fragments (Box 131)
  - Undated and unidentified (Box 131)
  - 1904 (Box 131)
- Letterpress copybooks
  - Central Pacific Railroad
    - Volume 1, June 20, 1868 - May 7, 1869 (Box 132)
    - Volume 2, May 7, 1869 - Jan. 19, 1870 (Box 132)
    - Volume 3, Jan. 20, 1870 - June 30, 1871 (Box 132A)
    - Volume 4, July 1, 1871 - Oct. 31, 1872 (Box 133)
    - Volume 5, Oct. 31, 1872 - Oct. 30, 1873 (Box 133)
    - Volume 6, Nov. 1, 1873 - Nov. 20, 1874 (Box 133)
    - Volume 7, Nov. 20, 1874 - Sept. 17, 1875 (Box 134)
    - Volume 8, Sept. 17, 1875 - July 31, 1876 (Box 134)
    - Volume 9, Aug. 1, 1876 - Aug. 9, 1877 (Box 134)
    - Volume 10, Aug. 9, 1877 - Jan. 31, 1879 (Box 135)
    - Volume 11, Feb. 1, 1879 - March 10, 1880 (Box 135)
    - Volume 12, March 13, 1880 - Nov. 23, 1880 (Box 135)
    - Volume 13, Nov. 23, 1880 - June 17, 1881 (Box 136)
    - Volume 14, June 18, 1881 - Jan. 7, 1882 (Box 136)
    - Volume 15, Jan. 7, 1882 - June 24, 1882 (Box 136)
    - Volume 16, June 26, 1882 - Nov. 24, 1882 (Box 137)
    - Volume 17, Nov. 25, 1882 - June 4, 1883 (Box 137)
    - Volume 18, June 4, 1883 - Feb. 4, 1884 (Box 137)
    - Volume 19, Feb. 4, 1884 - Jan. 30, 1885 (Box 138)
  - Central Pacific Railroad Company (Collis P. Huntington to Charles Crocker, Charles F. Crocker, Mark Hopkins, Leland Stanford, et al.)
    - Volume 20, June 23, 1868 - Aug. 5, 1869 (Box 138)
    - Volume 21, Aug. 5, 1869 - Dec. 5, 1870 (Box 138)
    - Volume 22, Dec. 6, 1870 - March 26, 1873 (Box 139)
    - Volume 23, April 2, 1873 - Aug. 15, 1874 (Box 139)
    - Volume 24, Aug. 17, 1874 - April 6, 1875 (Box 139)
    - Volume 25, April 6, 1875 - March 22, 1876 (Box 140)
    - Volume 26, March 23, 1876 - Sept. 19, 1877 (Box 140)
    - Volume 27, Sept. 20, 1877 - May 19, 1880 (Box 140)
    - Volume 28, May 20, 1880 - Sept. 29, 1881 (Box 141)
    - Volume 29, Sept. 29, 1881 - Dec. 13, 1882 (Box 141)
    - Volume 30, Dec. 15, 1882 - Dec. 1, 1883 (Box 141)
    - Volume 31, Dec. 4, 1883 - April 17, 1885 (Box 141)
    - Volume 32, April 21, 1885 - June 9, 1886 (Box 142)
    - Volume 33, June 11, 1886 - Nov. 21, 1887 (Box 142)
    - Volume 34, Nov. 22, 1887 - Jan. 4, 1889 (Box 142)
    - Volume 35, Jan. 4, 1889 - Aug. 27, 1891 (Box 142)
    - Volume 36, Aug. 31, 1891 - Nov. 19, 1891 (Box 143)
  - Central Pacific Railroad Company (Collis P. Huntington - Miscellaneous)
    - Volume 37, April 21, 1880 - April 15, 1881 (Box 143)
    - Volume 38, April 15, 1881 - Nov. 14, 1881 (Box 143)
    - Volume 39, Nov. 15, 1881 - June 14, 1882 (Box 143)
    - Volume 40, June 14, 1882 - May 26, 1883 (Box 144)
    - Volume 41, May 26, 1883 - Jan. 11, 1884 (Box 144)
    - Volume 42, Jan 12, 1884 - June 23, 1884 (Box 144)
    - Volume 43, June 23, 1884 - Feb. 10, 1885 (Box 144)
    - Volume 44, Feb. 12, 1885 - March 25, 1885 (Box 145)
  - Central Pacific Railroad Company (Isaac E. Gates)
    - Volume 45, Dec. 15, 1869 - Feb. 24, 1870 (Box 145)
    - Volume 46, Feb. 24, 1870 - July 6, 1870 (Box 145)
    - Volume 47, July 7, 1870 - March 9, 1871 (Box 145)
    - Volume 48, March 9, 1871 - Oct. 18, 1871 (Box 146)
    - Volume 49, Oct. 19, 1871 - July 5, 1872 (Box 146)
    - Volume 50, July 6, 1872 - Dec. 18, 1872 (Box 146)
    - Volume 51, Dec. 19, 1872 - May 20, 1873 (Box 147)
    - Volume 52, May 17, 1873 - Jan. 24, 1874 (Box 147)
    - Volume 53, Jan. 24, 1874 - July 9, 1874 (Box 147)
    - Volume 54, July 10, 1874 - Dec. 21, 1874 (Box 147)
    - Volume 55, Dec. 22, 1874 - May 12, 1875 (Box 148)
    - Volume 56, May 13, 1875 - Oct. 11, 1875 (Box 148)
    - Volume 57, Oct. 12, 1875 - Feb. 16, 1876 (Box 148)
    - Volume 58, Feb. 16, 1876 - June 12, 1876 (Box 148)
    - Volume 59, June 12, 1876 - Oct. 24, 1876 (Box 149)
    - Volume 60, Oct. 24, 1876 - March 1, 1877 (Box 149)
    - Volume 61, March 1, 1877 - June 13, 1877 (Box 149)
    - Volume 62, June 14, 1877 - Nov. 24, 1877 (Box 149)
    - Volume 63, Nov. 26, 1877 - March 1, 1878 (Box 150)
    - Volume 64, March 1, 1878 - June 17, 1878 (Box 150)
    - Volume 65, June 17, 1878 - Oct. 10, 1878 (Box 150)
    - Volume 66, Oct. 11, 1878 - Feb. 25, 1879 (Box 151)
    - Volume 67, Feb. 24, 1879 - June 11, 1879 (Box 151)
    - Volume 68, June 11, 1879 - Nov. 5, 1879 (Box 151)
    - Volume 69, Nov. 6, 1879 - March 6, 1880 (Box 151)
    - Volume 70, March 6, 1880 - Aug. 6, 1880 (Box 152)
    - Volume 71, Aug. 6, 1880 - Feb. 1, 1881 (Box 152)
    - Volume 72, Feb. 2, 1881 - June 21, 1881 (Box 152)
    - Volume 73, June 21, 1881 - Oct. 28, 1881 (Box 152)
    - Volume 74, Oct. 28, 1881 - Feb. 11, 1882 (Box 153)
    - Volume 75, Feb. 11, 1882 - May 2, 1882 (Box 153)
    - Volume 76, May 2, 1882 - July 18, 1882 (Box 153)
    - Volume 77, July 18, 1882 - Sept. 19, 1882 (Box 153)
    - Volume 78, Sept. 20, 1882 - Dec. 7, 1882 (Box 154)
    - Volume 79, Dec. 7, 1882 - Jan. 24, 1883 (Box 154)
    - Volume 80, Jan. 24, 1883 - March 21, 1883 (Box 154)
    - Volume 81, March 21, 1883 - May 16, 1883 (Box 154)
    - Volume 82, May 17, 1883 - July 24, 1883 (Box 155)
    - Volume 83, July 24, 1883 - Sept. 29, 1883 (Box 155)
    - Volume 84, Sept. 29, 1883 - Nov. 20, 1883 (Box 155)
    - Volume 85, Nov. 21, 1883 - Jan. 21, 1884 (Box 155)
    - Volume 86, Jan. 19, 1884 - March 4, 1884 (Box 156)
    - Volume 87, March 4, 1884 - April 14, 1884 (Box 156)
    - Volume 88, April 15, 1884 - June 10, 1884 (Box 156)
    - Volume 89, June 11, 1884 - July 31, 1884 (Box 156)
    - Volume 90, July 31, 1884 - Sept. 16, 1884 (Box 157)
    - Volume 91, Sept. 17, 1884 - Nov. 21, 1884 (Box 157)
    - Volume 92, Nov. 22, 1884 - Jan. 9, 1885 (Box 157)
    - Volume 93, Jan. 9, 1885 - Feb. 24, 1885 (Box 157)
    - Volume 94, Feb. 24, 1885 - April 13, 1885 (Box 158)
    - Volume 95, April 13, 1885 - July 8, 1885 (Box 158)
    - Volume 96, June, July 8, 1885 - Oct. 1885 (Box 158)
    - Volume 97, Oct. 7, 1885 - Jan. 21, 1886 (Box 158)
    - Volume 98, Jan. 21, 1886 - June 8, 1886 (Box 159)
    - Volume 99, May, June 8, 1886 - Sept. 10, 1886 (Box 159)
    - Volume 100, Sept. 10, 1886 - Feb. 9, 1887 (Box 159)
    - Volume 101, Feb. 9, 1887 - July 11, 1887 (Box 159)
    - Volume 102, July 12, 1887 - Jan. 27, 1888 (Box 160)
    - Volume 103, Jan. 28, 1888 - June 8, 1888 (Box 160)
    - Volume 104, June 9, 1888 - Oct. 24, 1888 (Box 160)
    - Volume 105, March 12, 1889 - Aug. 10, 1889 (Box 160)
    - Volume 106, July 31, 1889 - Dec. 5, 1889 (Box 161)
    - Volume 107, Nov., 1889 - April 25, 1890 (Box 161)
    - Volume 108, April 28, 1890 - Dec. 16, 1890 (Box 161)
    - Volume 109, Dec. 17, 1890 - Aug. 11, 1891 (Box 161)
    - Volume 110, Aug. 10, 1891 - Dec. 31, 1891 (Box 162)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company (Collis P. Huntington)
    - Volume 111, Nov. 2, 1870 - July 13, 1872 (Box 162)
    - Volume 112, July 22, 1872 - Aug. 22, 1873 (Box 162)
    - Volume 113, Aug. 22, 1873 - Feb. 4, 1874 (Box 163)
    - Volume 114, Feb. 10, 1874 - Oct. 17, 1874 (Box 163)
    - Volume 115, Oct. 17, 1874 - May 1, 1877 (Box 163)
    - Volume 116, May 7, 1877 - Dec. 2, 1879 (Box 163)
    - Volume 117, Dec. 2, 1879 - Feb. 16, 1881 (Box 164)
    - Volume 118, March 8, 1881 - Jan. 14, 1884 (Box 164)
    - Volume 119, April 19, 1880 - Jan. 8, 1881 (Box 164)
    - Volume 120, Jan. 10, 1881 - May 27, 1881 (Box 164)
    - Volume 121, May 27, 1881 - Sept. 17, 1881 (Box 165)
    - Volume 122, Sept. 17, 1881 - Feb. 1, 1882 (Box 165)
    - Volume 123, Feb. 1, 1882 - June 10, 1882 (Box 165)
    - Volume 124, June 10, 1882 - Dec. 30, 1882 (Box 165)
    - Volume 125, Jan. 1, 1883 - June 9, 1883 (Box 166)
    - Volume 126, June 11, 1883 - Jan. 10, 1884 (Box 166)
    - Volume 127, Jan. 12, 1884 - Oct. 10, 1884 (Box 166)
    - Volume 128, Oct. 10, 1884 - May 29, 1885 (Box 166)
    - Volume 129, May 30, 1885 - Nov. 30, 1885 (Box 167)
    - Volume 130, Dec. 1, 1885 - Feb. 16, 1886 (Box 167)
    - Volume 131, Feb. 15, 1886 - May 27, 1886 (Box 167)
    - Volume 132, May 27, 1886 - July 30, 1886 (Box 167)
  - Chesapeake Dry Dock and Construction Company
    - Volume 133, June 1, 1891 - Dec. 21, 1891 (Box 168)
  - Chesapeake, Ohio and Southwestern Railroad Company
    - Volume 134, June 8, 1881 - Feb. 13, 1882 (Box 168)
    - Volume 135, Feb. 16, 1882 - Nov. 14, 1882 (Box 168)
    - Volume 136, Nov. 16, 1882 - Aug. 15, 1883 (Box 168)
    - Volume 137, Aug. 15, 1883 - Aug. 16, 1884 (Box 169)
    - Volume 138, Aug. 19, 1884 - Dec. 26, 1885 (Box 169)
    - Volume 139, Dec. 10, 1885 - July 22, 1886 (Box 169)
  - Congo, railroad, proposed
    - Volume 140, June 19, 1889 - Feb. 6, 1890 (Box 169)
  - Contracting and Building Company
    - Volume 141, July 2, 1879 - June 11, 1881 (Box 170)
    - Volume 142, June 11, 1881 - March 13, 1885 (Box 170)
    - Volume 143, March 5, 1886 - Oct. 19, 1886 (Box 170)
    - Volume 144, Oct. 18, 1886 - Feb. 25, 1887 (Box 170)
    - Volume 145, Feb. 25, 1887 - June 22, 1887 (Box 171)
    - Volume 146, June 22, 1887 - Dec. 14, 1887 (Box 171)
    - Volume 147, Dec. 14, 1887 - May 23, 1888 (Box 171)
    - Volume 148, May 24, 1888 - Dec. 3, 1888 (Box 171)
    - Volume 149, Dec. 3, 1888 - Nov. 17, 1893 (Box 172)
  - Contracting and Building Company (Collis P. Huntington)
    - Volume 150, April 2, 1886 - May 23, 1888 (Box 172)
    - Volume 151, May 26, 1888 - Dec. 16, 1891 (Box 172)
  - Elizabethtown, Lexington and Big Sandy Railroad Company
    - Volume 152, June 17, 1871 - Sept. 3, 1874 (Box 172)
  - Elizabethtown, Lexington and Big Sandy Railroad Company (Collis P. Huntington-Miscellaneous)
    - Volume 153, April 19, 1880 - March 3, 1881 (Box 173)
    - Volume 154, March 3, 1881 - Sept. 20, 1881 (Box 173)
    - Volume 155, Sept. 30, 1881 - Sept. 27, 1882 (Box 173)
    - Volume 156, Sept. 25, 1882 - April 14, 1884 (Box 173)
    - Volume 157, April 15, 1884 - April 22, 1885 (Box 174)
    - Volume 158, April 23, 1885 - Feb. 25, 1886 (Box 174)
    - Volume 159, Feb. 25, 1886 - July 20, 1886 (Box 174)
  - Kentucky Central Railroad Company and Chesapeake and Nashville Railroad Company
    - Volume 160, Aug. 2, 1886 - Dec. 28, 1891 (Box 174)
  - Louisville, New Orleans and Texas Railroad Company
    - Volume 161, March 8, 1883 - Dec. 14, 1891 (Box 175)
  - Mississippi Valley Construction Company
    - Volume 162, Aug. 7, 1885 - Nov. 11, 1889 (Box 175)
  - Newport News and Mississippi Valley Company
    - Volume 163, Aug. 2, 1886 - Dec. 20, 1886 (Box 175)
    - Volume 164, Dec. 20, 1886 - March 18, 1887 (Box 175)
    - Volume 165, March 17, 1887 - Oct. 28, 1887 (Box 176)
    - Volume 166, Oct. 28, 1887 - Jan. 21, 1888 (Box 176)
    - Volume 167, Jan. 23, 1888 - Dec. 11, 1888 (Box 176)
    - Volume 168, Oct. 29, 1888 - Nov. 30, 1889 (Box 176)
    - Volume 169, Dec. 2, 1889 - June 29, 1891 (Box 177)
    - Volume 170, July 7, 1891 - Jan. 2, 1892 (Box 177)
  - Oregonian Railroad Company
    - Volume 171, Jan. 28, 1890 - Jan. 29, 1891 (Box 177)
  - Scioto Valley Railroad Company
    - Volume 172, Aug. 20, 1886 - Dec. 4, 1890 (Box 177)
  - Southern Development Company
    - Volume 173, May 3, 1881 - Oct. 9, 1882 (Box 178)
  - Southern Pacific Company
    - Volume 174, May 20, 1885 - Aug. 27, 1885 (Box 178)
    - Volume 175, Aug. 28, 1885 - Nov. 24, 1885 (Box 178)
    - Volume 176, Nov. 27, 1885 - Feb. 19, 1886 (Box 178)
    - Volume 177, Feb. 19, 1886 - May 19, 1886 (Box 179)
    - Volume 178, May 19, 1886 - Nov. 23, 1886 (Box 179)
    - Volume 179, Nov. 22, 1886 - Feb. 28, 1887 (Box 179)
    - Volume 180, March 1, 1887 - Sept. 28, 1887 (Box 179)